powermax.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | PowerMax

## **1\. Introduction**

### 1.1. Purpose of policy

**PowerMax**  (“us,” “we,” or **”PowerMax”** ) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors to and users of the website. We created this Website Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site and the editorial, ecommerce and interactive services available from the Site and from other websites that we operate (such services and sites being referred to herein collectively as the “Service”), and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Policy is only applicable to the Site and the Service.  This Policy does not apply to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy, nor does it apply to any services that may be offered by our business partners, where your personally identifiable information is collected by anyone other than PowerMax.

### 1.2. Notice concerning children

PLEASE NOTE: We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online.

### 1.3. Disclaimer regarding site contents

REMEMBER: We have created this Site and the Service for the purpose of providing products, services, news, and information that we believe will educate and benefit our users, and while we are always doing our best to monitor the information on this Site and to update the Site regularly, we cannot guarantee the accuracy, currency, reliability or completeness of any information or material included here, or on any site accessible from here.  We expect that you will use your own skill and care in using the Site and in communicating with other users and purchasing any products or services that may be available from the Site. In order to use the Site and the Service, you must review and agree to our Terms of Use, which include this Policy and which also include important terms regarding the materials that we make available on the Site and through the Service.

WE DO NOT PRE-SCREEN OR APPROVE USERS, AND WE CANNOT GUARANTEE USER IDENTITIES OR ANY INFORMATION THAT USERS PROVIDE. WE HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY ACTIONS YOU MAY TAKE ON OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE OR THE SERVICE.  YOU SHOULD NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO ANY OTHER USER UNLESS YOU KNOW WHO THAT USER IS AND KNOW WHAT HE OR SHE INTENDS TO DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.  SIMILARLY, YOU SHOULD NOT PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO VENDORS OR BUSINESS PARTNERS OF POWERMAX WITHOUT CONFIRMING THE IDENTITIES OF THOSE VENDORS OR BUSINESS PARTNERS AND REVIEWING THE PRIVACY POLICIES THAT THEY HAVE IN EFFECT.

## **2\. Information Collection Practices**

### 2.1. What personal information did we collect?

In operating the Site and providing the Service, we may collect a variety of user-submitted information such as names, email addresses, and other contact information, in order to establish and authenticate user accounts, to enable ecommerce transactions, to facilitate certain interactive features we offer, to enable interactions between users, and to send information and notices to our users regarding the Site and the Service. In addition, we may provide registration forms, bulletin boards, comment forms, online surveys, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, e-mail addresses, mobile phone numbers and other contact information, as well as information related to the subject matter of the activities requiring registration, the surveys or of the other online forms.  Also, if you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our bulletin boards, comment areas, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as personal information.

### 2.2. What additional information did we collect?

(a) AUTOMATIC COLLECTION. Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses. No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Site may also gather anonymous “traffic data” that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.  
(b) COOKIES. From time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to the Site. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of the Site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at the Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

## **3.  Use and Sharing Practices**

### 3.1. What do we do with collected information?

a) PERSONAL INFORMATION. You always have the option not to provide us with any personal information. Your decision not to do so, however, may limit your ability to access areas of the Site or features of the Service that require an account and/or a user name and password. If you do elect to provide any personal information to us, then we will use that personal information to provide you with access to the Site and the services offered by us or to comply with the law, and we may share that information as follows:  
(1) We share demographic data (such as zip codes, user ages and income information) with advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate (i.e., non-personally-identifiable) basis.  
(2) We will generally require personal information from our users who purchase products or services from the Site; while the specific nature of the information required will vary depending on the transaction, in most cases that information will include, at a minimum, the purchaser’s name, email address, mailing address, and possibly credit card information. In order to complete the transaction, we may also need to share this information with the relevant third-party vendor supplying the products or services.  
(3) You can notify us at any time that you want to terminate your PowerMax account and our storage of your personal information, and upon receipt of that notice, we will remove all information about you from our customer database, at which point you will no longer be able to access any of our services that require registration unless you re-register.  
In addition, we may use your personal information to verify your identity, to check your qualifications, or to follow up with transactions initiated on the Site. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to the Site or the Service, or to send you additional information about us.  
(b) ANONYMOUS INFORMATION. We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.  
(c) USE OF COOKIES. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your user ID or password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, or for other purposes. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.  
(d) DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. In addition to disclosures described above, we may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the requirements of applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or our parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates, (2) protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of users of the Site, or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site.  
(e) SALE OF INFORMATION. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell our company or portions of our company or sell or buy portions of other companies or assets, including the information collected through the Site. If PowerMax or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.

## **4.  Security**

PowerMax, the Site and the Service have security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, or alteration, and we and our owners, partners and affiliates will have no liability to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

## **5.  Websites beyond our control**

### 5.1. Public forums

The Site may include, or the Service may offer you access to, interactive forums such as blogs, message boards and comment areas. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and please exercise caution when using any of these public forums to disclose your personal information.  We have no control over the use of any personal information disclosed in a public forum, and you are solely responsible for the effects of any such disclosure.

### 5.2. Third party websites

The Site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.  In addition, in no event will we have any responsibility for the contents of those other websites, and you visit and use those websites entirely at your own risk. 

## **6.  Contact information and policy updates**

### 6.1. Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to this Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database please feel free to contact us.

### 6.2. Updates and changes

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.
